<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>My Travels</title>
    <link>https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>i’m leaving the pictures but whatever here’s the ingredients info for go-gurt:&lt;br/&gt;Cultured Grade A Nonfat Milk, Sugar, Modified Food Starch. Contains 1% or less of: Kosher Gelatin, Tricalcium Phosphate, Corn Starch, Vegetable and Fruit Juice (for color), Potassium Sorbate Added to Maintain Freshness, Natural Flavor, Vitamin A Acetate, Vitamin D3.&lt;br/&gt;Contains milk ingredients.&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.1</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Blog_files/rbds_77B.jpg</url>
      <title>My Travels</title>
      <link>https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Apple’s autogenerated filler post</title>
      <link>https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Entries/2025/10/16_Apples_autogenerated_filler_post.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b263a4f-d36d-4191-b933-30840ff858e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:42:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Entries/2025/10/16_Apples_autogenerated_filler_post_files/rbhh_0053B.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Media/object001_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:364px; height:173px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Consectetuer arcu ipsum ornare pellentesque vehicula, in vehicula diam, ornare magna erat felis wisi a risus. Justo fermentum id. Malesuada eleifend, tortor molestie, a fusce a vel et. Mauris at suspendisse, neque aliquam faucibus adipiscing, vivamus in. Wisi mattis leo suscipit nec amet, nisl fermentum tempor ac a, augue in eleifend in venenatis, cras sit id in vestibulum felis in, sed ligula. In sodales suspendisse mauris quam etiam erat, quia tellus convallis eros rhoncus diam orci, porta lectus esse adipiscing posuere et, nisl arcu vitae laoreet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Zelus torqueo velit ad suscipit vindico luptatum premo. Ut metuo suscipere autem suscipit si fere facilisi abluo ille. Mos duis, rusticus facilisis inhibeo suscipit loquor indoles, sagaciter opto capto, premo. Regula os, ea zelus torqueo ideo, consectetuer, iustum jugis. Roto usitas eros laoreet exerci utrum patria similis illum adipiscing. Ulciscor, tation utinam ut molior et, te in aliquip. Nostrud nostrud ratis antehabeo incassum jus abdo vicis adipiscing nostrud.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dignissim hendrerit similis amet quis abico oppeto appellatio conventio suscipit haero commodo.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Entries/2025/10/16_Apples_autogenerated_filler_post_files/rbhh_0053B.jpg" length="34583" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i didn’t study for my precalc test and all i got was this lousy website</title>
      <link>https://evanium.github.io/Evanium/Blog/Entries/2025/10/16_i_didnt_study_for_my_precalc_test_and_all_i_got_was_this_lousy_website.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83837877-dc9a-4fd2-bc75-434f549041bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:42:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>I actually kinda like this app shame it’s from the dinosaur ages. Don’t ask why I own a 2010 MacBook too, because I don’t know. Anyways i’m listening to Radiohead because Radiohead is cool and like this song is great. Now I’m going to add nonsense to this web page please enjoy whatever I add below.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
